So currently the work class contains two string variables, one for
当前 Word 类包含两个字符串变量
the default translation and one for the Miwok translation.
一个用于默认的译文 一个用于米沃克语译文
And both of these variables are private, but we have public methods
这两个变量都是私有变量 但是具有公共方法
that other classes can call to get access to the state of the object.
其他类可以调用这些方法来访问对象的状态
So now to add support for images, we're going to need to
要添加图片支持 我们需要
add a new variable to keep track of the image associated with each word object.
添加新的变量来跟踪与每个 Word 对象相关联的图片
Well what should the data type of this new variable be?
这个新变量的数据类型应该是什么呢？
Well we could store the actual image but that actually takes up a lot of
我们可以存储实际的图片 但是这会占用太多的内存
memory because all our illustrations are not trivial in size.
因为所有的插图都不是很小
Plus for
此外
a really long list of words, if we ever scroll to the bottom of the list.
对于非常长的单词列表 如果我们浏览到列表末端
It would be a waste to store each image in the word list
那么存储单词列表中的每个图片会浪费内存
if the images have strolled off screen.
因为有些图片已经不在屏幕上
Plus it would blot the amount of memory resources that the word list would use.
而且会增加单词列表用到的内存资源量
Now, a more efficient way is to just store the resource ID for each image.
更加高效的方式是存储每个图片的资源 ID
A resource ID something like R.drawable.number_one is
R.drawable.number_one 等资源 ID
actually an integer.
实际上是个整数
So instead of storing an actual image,
我们可以存储资源的名称以便以后找到该资源
we just store the name of the resource so that we can find it later.
而不是存储实际的图片
So we can think of that situation like an address book.
我们可以将这种情形想象为通讯簿
You don't need to store someone's whole house into your address book.
你不需要将某个人的整个房子都存储到地址簿里
Instead you can just store someone's mailing address.
而是存储对方的邮寄地址
And in case you need it later.
以后需要这些信息的时候
You can look up that mailing address and go find their house.
可以查找该邮寄地址并找到对方的房子
So back to our situation, when the list view asked for
回到我们的案例 当 ListView 需要
a list item layout for this word.
该单词的列表项布局时
It's the word adapter's responsibility to return the resource ID, so
WordAdapter 需要负责返回该资源 ID
something like R.drawable.number_one.
类似于 R.drawable.number_one
And turn it into an actual image of an acorn that will be displayed onto
将其转换为实际的橡子图片
the screen.
并在屏幕上展示该图片
So we see here that each word class holds two strings and one integer for
在这里可以看到 每个 Word 类包含两个字符串和
the image resource ID.
一个表示图片资源 ID 的整数
So to follow the convention for
为了遵守该类中其他变量的规则
the other variables in this class, we want these state variables
我们希望这些状态变量
to be declared with the private access modifier and not public.
声明为私有访问修饰符 而不是公共修饰符
So this means that only methods within this class can access these
意味着只有该类里面的方法可以访问
private variables.
这些私有变量
So, we can trust that methods within this class will modify the image
我们可以信任该类里面的方法将正确地
resource ID properly.
修改图片资源 ID
We don't want the variable to be public, because other classes
我们不希望该变量是公共的 因为其他类
could change the image resource ID into something invalid, which would cause our
可能会将该图片资源 ID 更改为无效的值
app to crash when we try to translate the resource ID into an actual image.
这样当我们尝试将该资源 ID 转换为实际图片时 应用会崩溃
Now back to the first question of the quiz
回到测试题的第一个问题
which asked what additional state what a word object contain?
Word 对象应该还要包含什么状态？
Well we'll need a private integer variable for the image resource ID.
我们需要为图片资源 ID 提供一个私有整数变量
And since this variable's private, we need a public method so
因为该变量是私有的 我们需要一个公共方法
that other classes can access the image associated with this word object.
这样其他类才能够访问与该 Word 对象关联的图片
And by the way,
此外
only create public access modifiers to access private variables.
仅在你希望其他类来访问这些方法时
If you intend for other classes to need those methods.
创建公共访问修饰符来访问私有变量
If we created additional variables for
如果我们为自己创建额外的变量
ourselves to manage the word object internally.
在内部管理 Word 对象
They don't need to be external facing.
这些变量则不需要面向外部
We don't need to create public get methods
我们不需要创建公共获取方法
to expose those variables to outside callers.
使这些变量暴露于外部调用函数
So back to the second question of the quiz that asked,
回到测试题的第二个问题
what additional method should we have?
我们应该还要采用哪些方法？
We would need a public method called getImageResourceId
我们需要一个公共方法 叫做 getImageResourceId
to return the integer image resource ID.
来返回整型图片资源 ID